The End
Oh, my God.
Nice!
That has got to be a new
world record for butts.
I guess I'm the official
butt cleaner here.
Come on!
Oh, just a little bit of tar juice.
Damn you, Yanni!
Are you out of your fucking mouth?
Yeah?
I didn't mix up what Brent
was doing again, did I?
Screaming back.
Just be careful next time!
Huh, huh, huh?
Yeah?
Well, looks like it's
somebody's lucky day.
A little moist, but listen,
a butt is a butt, am I right?
Whatever is fine.
Oh! Nice! Nice!
Nice kitty!
Soft kitty!
Why, God, why?
Sonate, Sonate, Sonate,
Sonate, Sonate, Sonate, Sonate, Sonate,
Sonate,
Son
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
If it's over, if it's over, if it's
over, I'll just be able to get it.
If it's over, I'll just be able to get it.
3401!
3401! 3401!
Yeah!
tiny problem a fresh pack of cigarettes
doesn't have any gaps in it thing is in
their natural form these little babies
are packed in here to the brim it takes
about five cigarettes and then you've
got a perfect marshmallowy home for your
cheapo lighter if you ask me this is how
every single box of cigarettes should
They're perfect but oh
so temporary dang it
they packed this one
pretty tight it looks like
Ouch, meowsing, finding the
world's cruelty is my superpower.
The three second rule, they didn't
all get covered in sidewalk poo.
But he's tight this month too.
Maybe it's fine if I
just cut off the tips.
James Smoker Cat!
Beast Folk Temps, listen up.
Eyes up here, please.
Here's what you all will
be taking care of today.
And by the way, we prohibit all types
of tobacco products at our facility,
so we'll take that till your shift ends.
Oh, my God.
Huh?
Where the hell did number 56 go?
Oh, she's long gone. What?
All that cat had was 30 more minutes!
Give it to me!
Are you the Beast Folk
gig worker helping today?
The vase you'll be cleaning is
considered a national treasure.
I need you to be very careful.
I don't want to see a speck of dust.
And don't get your animal smell on it.
Consider it done.
How could it possibly be dirtier
than before you started cleaning it?
And it smells like it's been sitting
in front of a disgusting train station.
You waste of space!
I've got a whole hundred and seventy
yen to my name and six cigarettes.
And it'll be six days
till my next part-time job
I have to find a way to live on only 28
yen a day One cigarette every 24 hours
I bet I can just make it
This is my first and last of the day
When I smoke, I feel like I'm trouble-free
Yeah, making it six days on a hundred
and seventy yen ain't no thing
Maybe just one more
I should have figured
Well, I guess just a sig a
day is harder in its own way.
Probably easier to just go cold turkey.
Why does this always happen to me?
Always, always, always!
I have zero freaking self-control!
I know I'm not perfect,
but for fuck's sake!
Someone up there is
still looking out for me!
1,160 yen.
Hello? Yanni? Hi!
I'm glad you called.
How have you been?
All good here.
Just wanted to see what you were
up to and hear your voices all.
Well, that's sweet.
It's been a while since
I've seen you, so, you know.
Oh, want to come over and hang out a bit?
Let's not get crazy.
Wait, what?
True or false, your entire
apartment smells awful.
The floors are totally
not covered in ashes.
How'd you know?
That's crazy.
Just grab your phone
and send me a pic, then.
Let me take a look at your pristine place.
It's what I thought.
Bye.
I can't clean up.
Pristine it is.
Just got to start with gathering the
trash, but I need a trash bag to do that.
What about the stale on the floor?
Who cares?
I'll cover them up so I can start with the
cigarette butts in the
mold colony in the fridge.
Then maybe she'll run out of the toilet
and she'll never come over all alone.
I can't breathe.
I'm a bad luck magnet.
Just one.
Half of one.
Where's my lighter?
I see a lot of smoking potential here.
Yes!
Thank you, God!
You've made me the happiest cat on Earth!
Now that right there is some good luck.
She sent one.
Look who won fastest room clean-up today.
Not the tidiest room I've ever
seen. A for effort, though.
Poop.
When family starts making a stink,
then it might be time to try a
little harder to quit smoking.
Yeah, readin' can just fuck off.
Mm, and boop. Hmm.
If one works great, then
how about more than one?
What?
You haven't touched a
cigarette in three whole days?
That's what happens when I try.
The way you were smoking,
you'd think your lungs survived
on nicotine instead of oxygen.
I'm so proud of you.
No biggie. It is.
This has got to be the single
greatest accomplishment of your life.
You're making me blush, sis.
Weeks day after new
beers are so the bestest.
Oh, I'm seeing smoke!
This is giving me good omen vibes!
Uh, what is it?
You need something, you walking ashtray?
I'm just spreading all the good vibes.
Hey.
I need booze and I need
cigarettes, you hear me?
Why don't you go get me some?
But I'm really trying to
finish my work right now.
You little bookworm.
All that learning making you
feel like a big shot, did it?
Get your head out of all these books.
The second you finish middle school,
you're going straight to work!
But I...
I bust my hump to make sure you've
got a roof over your freakin' head!
You'd think a kid would be
grateful and get his old man...
GOOSERIES!
You in there?
Oh, for crying out loud.
I can't believe my own
fleshing blood would gang
up on me with a landlord
to tell me how much I reek.
Taking a bath is nothing
more than moist pain.
Pain up my butt.
But once you get in the water,
you do feel pretty refreshed, huh?
A bath's like a car wash for your soul.
You know, I might be earning
my clean freak badge.
Mm-mm.
The bath is the yin, and having a
smoke afterwards is a tasty yang.
Man, it's chilly, and my throat hurts.
Awesome, don't tell me I'm sick now
Yeah, that's definitely a cold
Cigarettes tastes like trash
so smoking is out the window
Just take me sleep
I can barely get through menthols.
Oh!
Huh?
Help!
Oh, please don't!
You just had to run away, huh?
After I came all this
way to check up on you?
You look like a secret agent
from the health department.
You gotta admit, people don't
usually show up in hazmat suits.
Well, stop reeking of cigarettes then.
And it is okay to clean up after yourself.
Cigarettes and garbage
make a pretty stinky team.
How bad are you feeling now?
I'm doing a little better than yesterday.
Let me go make you some Ray's porridge.
She could be a little nicer.
Nobody made her come visit me.
Guess that means she's got a
soft spot for me after all.
The porridge is ready!
Are you okay, Yanni?
Oh, I'm so sorry. Oh, my.
Oh, the mask. I need it.
Oh, my God, no.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Is it really, uh, stinky?
That actually hurts my feelings a little.
Well, looky here.
Howdy, Emoko.
Oh, Kansai, hi, how are you?
Thanks for always looking
out for my sister.
That's sweet of you to say.
Are you really that
thing's youngest sister?
So what you up to?
Big sis got some sort
of bug and feels gross.
And little sis doesn't
want to get sick too.
Aw, coming all that way
just to help her out.
Who would believe that thing
could even catch a cold?
It's funny, but she's pretty
good at catching a cold.
Like when she eats 50
popsicles in one sitting?
Or jumps into the snow in her pajamas?
And when she gets sick, I
always have to take care of her.
That sounds pretty rough!
Yeah, it's not the easiest.
A shame you have to come all that way.
I can help you out, all
you gotta do is call me.
Appreciate the offer, but I can't.
I know how much of a burden
she can end up being sometimes.
So I think it's best for everyone if
I'm the one who takes care of her.
Well, aren't you adorable you're so
cute I could adapt you wait what?
She's going to die that's for certain
She's got two months to live.
Could even make it three.
Maybe a bit longer is possible, too.
About a hundred days.
A hundred... cats?
Oh, Imoko!
Don't you dare make my little sis cry!
But it's your lungs that
are making her cry, though.
I get it.
It's crystal clear.
We all die one day.
Pretty simple equation.
No smoking in the fucking
hospital, you goddamn beast folk!
A dream?
It was a dream, right?
Lung cancer in a hundred
days was just a dream.
Hey, you.
I'm alright.
Yeah.
I mean, it's nothing.
I just, I wanted to chat, that's all.
Sorry to bother you.
It's…
It's… Little sis…
I…
I'm gonna quit smoking for real this time!
It's beautiful.
It almost looks like cigarette smoke.
So yummy!
Thank you.